# **Ngandu Dadou**

Phone: +27 78 642 54 45
LinkedIn: Ngandu D
Email: Dadyngandu20@gmail.com

#### **Profile**

I am an excellent candidate with an excellent problem solving skills, empathy listener, reliable, flexible and adaptable to change. I have a strong commitment to privacy and confidentiality, attention to detail and time management skills, strong communication skills in both French and English, strong people management skills including leadership, interpersonal skills, approach to process improvement, and self-confidence.

I have a background in building strong customer relationships.

I realize that customers are the most important part of building a business, and keeping customers satisfied can lead to sustaining loyal customers. My experience in the service industry has taught me how to both reach and exceed customer expectations and provide service that they can count on. I am a focused person, and I am always willing to go beyond the minimum expectations to make sure I serve customer needs. I approach new situations with enthusiasm and enjoy the challenge of learning something new in my work.

#### **Education**

> 2021

Institution: Cape Peninsula University of Technology

Course: Computer System

> 2017

Institution: Kingsway College

Course: Management

> 2016

Institution: University of Cape Town English Centre

Course: English

> 2015

Institution: INPP/Kinshasa

Course: Informatique Maintenance

**>** 2013

Institution: Mama wa Boboto College Highest grade passed: Grade 12-Matric

### **Professional Experience**

Company: MindPearl (Swiss & Bruxelles Airlines)
 January 2022-Present
 Assist Passengers with all travel related service and enquiries (outbound and inbound)

Achieve and maintain optimal accessibility to passengers to in order to achieve performance targets.

Provide excellent and consistent service to ensure service quality in dealing with pax all the times.

Maintain product knowledge at all the times to ensure consistent customer satisfaction.

#### Company : Lufthansa

March 2019- January 2022

Mentoring and helping newly recruited customer service consultant to practice the customer interactions and listening skills, building their self-confident and good identification of the customer needs in order to maintain a better communication as per the company standard and deliver a good quality service to the customers on their requests.

As an accessor this role means being in collaboration with the team quality department by evaluating customer service consultant calls, in order to maintain the standard knowledge as per the company requirement as well as following up on their personal development.

Company : Bidvest Bank Internship of 6 months

Digital marketing and making sure customers are able to manage the Bank App and all transactions.

Company: Kloof Street House

2016-2018 /part-time job

Implemented new menu introduce strategies, increasing customer purchase of wine and desert by 10%. Bussed tables, presented menus seated customers and assisted waiters with drinks orders, ensuring that customers enjoyed a pleasant, hygienic dining experience.

Company : Arauphar Production/Kinshasa DRC

2014-2015

Position: Stock Manager

Implemented new menu introduce strategies, increasing customer purchase of wine and desert by 10%. Bussed tables, presented menus seated customers and assisted waiters with drinks orders, ensuring that customers enjoyed a pleasant, hygienic dining experience.

#### **References**

 Kloof Street House Restaurant Reference name: Nathan (HR)

Location: Kloof Street, Cape Town 8001

Contact: +2781 590 9879

Arauphar Production

Reference name : Michel (GM) Location : Kinshasa, DRC Contact : +243 910 684 397 Mind Pearl

Reference name: Francois Position: Team Leader Contact: +27826205192

Location: Cape Town City Centre, Cape Town 8000

## **Skills**

- Management project
- Photoshop
- Video Editor
- Microsoft Office
- Excel
- Bilingual
- Excellence Communication skills